Oh, hi. I do apologize. I am trying to
record.
However, I made Diane the cohost.
Oh, we're back on.
>> Okay. Now I see the recording light is back on.
Awesome. Okay.
>> Yeah. Whatever it was hit the fiber backbone,
so that's kind of annoying.
Hey.
I mean, since Amanda's back, maybe we can
continue.
>> Do we want to pick off where
we left off?
Public speaking? That would be appropriate.
>> I think continuing with public speak would be
you know, nice and we can work with what we have. What do you think? Yes, I agree. Let's Let's do it. Rajon.
>> Okay. And it is recording?
Yes. I see the lights on.
>> So Mark just emailed me and said he cannot
oh, no. There he is. He's showing back up.
We might have Mark again.
Hey, Rob. Okay.
>> Yeah. I I never dropped off. I was always here. I just killed my video because I haven't eaten yet. Alright. Can we continue with public speak? I think we have a quorum on.
Alright. So
I believe Did we lose
>> Did we lose Amanda again?
Yeah. Did we lose Amanda again? Yeah. We did. But it's recording. So
>> who haven't sorry. I missed a bunch, obviously, because I have no idea where we left off. I'm totally lost. Thought I thought Karen was speaking at the time.
Okay.
But Erin's gone.
Okay. We've lost her. Okay.
>> So
So Caitlin hasn't spoken.
Caitlin, do you wanna speak?
>> Yes,
please. If you guys can hear me. Yes. We can. Okay.